Boyd Hinds Papers
Hartford History Center, Hartford Public Library
- Series II: Political Career
  - Box 33 - Boyd Hinds--Legislative Records--Bill Drafts (2)
    - Materials describing what happens to a bill
  - Box 34 - Boyd Hinds--Legislative Records--Correspondence and Research
    - Bill summary, 1977
    - Meeting notes, 1976-1979
    - Assembly correspondence, 1976-1980
    - Reporting on poverty - clipping file, 1983
    - Correspondence with prisoners - rights abuses, 1977-1979
    - Constituent letters, 1979
    - Fire reports - Hartford, 1976-1977
    - Keney Park
    - Police Community Safety committee
    - Replies to questionnaire, 1977
  - Box 35 - Boyd Hinds--Legislative Records--Research--Misc. (1)
    - Rules governing the Democratic Party, Hartford, 1975
    - Asbestos in schools, 1979
    - Alcoholism and treatment (Beacon Detox Center)
    - CT guaranteed tax base grant
    - Liquor bill
    - Equal Rights Amendment
    - 1974 welfare pledge
    - General Employment Assistance Program, 1978
  - Box 36 - Boyd Hinds--Legislative Records--Research--Misc. (2)
    - 8th Assembly District Organization
    - Governor's Council on Spanish-Speaking Opportunities, 1976
    - I-91/I-291 renovation materials, 1977
    - Environmental study of I-91 and I-291 maps, 1977
    - Environmental study of I-91 and I-291, 1977
    - Title XX survey, 1977
    - PUCA rate hike hearing, 1/26/1978
    - Employment opportunities initiatives, 1978
  - Box 37 - Boyd Hinds--8th District Assembly, 1976-1978
    - 1976 Absentee ballot log
    - CT General Assembly: Legislative Record Index. Final Edition, 1976
    - 8th General Assembly political seminar
    - Subcommittee 1 – General Government, 1977
    - Subcommittees and the agencies under them, 1977
    - State agency questionnaire, 1977
    - State sheets, 1977
    - The statutes: 4-61c-4-61s
    - Calendar of hearings, 1977
    - Script for hearings, 1977
    - Social work licensure materials, 1977
    - Democratic Town Committee funding reports, 1977
    - Chamber Political Action Committee bylaws
    - Boyd Hinds--UCONN Health Center speech, 10/24/77
    - Municipal Revitalization Act, 1976
    - Amendments to Small Business Act
    - Housing allowance bill, 10/24/77
    - Report of Unemployment in the North-End of Hartford, 1979
  - Box 38 - Boyd Hinds--8th District Assembly, 1978-1980
    - State of Connecticut Commendations (assorted)
    - Democratic Campaign Planning Institute, 1978
    - 1979 Legislative Session – Misc. Materials
    - Sexual Orientation – UCC Research, 1979
    - Legislative Commendation and Recommendations, 1978-1979
    - Abortion Lit- UCC, 1979
    - Hinds Assembly Work - United Technologies vs. Ray Marshall et al, 1979
    - Health Center Budget, 1980
    - Boyd Hinds – Property Tax Research, 1980-1981
  - Box 39 - Greater Hartford Bsiness Development Center -Loan Applications 1982. RESTRICTED
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (Part 1), 1982
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (Part 2), 1982
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (Part 3), 1982
  - Box 40 - Greater Hartford Bsiness Development Center -Loan Applications 1983. RESTRICTED
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (1), 1983
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (2), 1983
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (3), 1983
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (4), 1983
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (5), 1983
  - Box 41 - Greater Hartford Bsiness Development Center -Loan Applications 1984. RESTRICTED
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (1), 1984
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (2), 1984
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (3), 1984
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (4), 1984
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (5), 1984
  - Box 42 - Greater Hartford Bsiness Development Center -Loan Applications 1985. RESTRICTED
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (1), 1985
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (2), 1985
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (3), 1985
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (4), 1985
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (5), 1985
  - Box 43 - Greater Hartford Bsiness Development Center -Loan Applications 1986. RESTRICTED
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (1), 1986
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (2), 1986
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (3), 1986
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (4), 1986
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (5), 1986
  - Box 44 - Greater Hartford Bsiness Development Center -Loan Applications 1987. RESTRICTED
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (1), 1987
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (2), 1987
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (3), 1987
    - Greater Hartford Business Development Center – Loan Applications (4), 1987
    - Greater Hartford Business Community Development Co.
    - Greater Hartford Process Records
- Series III. Personal
  - Box 45 - Personal
    - Tolkien - book manuscript, undated
    - Boyd Hinds newspaper clippings
    - Boyd Hinds newspaper clippings
    - Boyd Hinds - house map
  - Box 46 - Boyd Hinds Book Collection
    - George Cooper, Harriet Rabb, et al., ed. Fair Employment Litigation: Texts and Materials for Student and Practitioner. 1975
    - The 1979 Supplement to the Ruzicho Civil Rights Litigation Manual
    - W.E. Dubois. The Souls of Black Folk, 1961
    - Edward C. Hayes. Power Structure and Urban Policy: Who Rules in Oakland?, 1972
    - Ernest Patterson. Black City Politics, 1974
    - James O. Wilson, ed. Urban Renewal: The Record and the Controversy, 1961
    - Nathan Wright. Jr. Let’s Face Racism! A Youth Forum Book, 1970
    - Nathan Wright. Jr. Let’s Face Racism! A Youth Forum Book, 1970
    - Nathan Wright. Jr. Let’s Face Racism! A Youth Forum Book (copy 2), 1970